favicon.cc 2014-12-23

# favicon.ico Generator

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on favicon.cc. 

When registering on our site, you are asked to enter your name and email address. You may, however, visit favicon.cc anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on favicon.cc. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to favicon.cc and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To deliver the service  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the service requested.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Data protection

We would like to ensure that your use of our internet pages is secure and satisfactory. We make every effort to ensure compliance with current data protection rulings. If you decide to give us or our business associates personal data via the internet, e.g. so that correspondence can be processed or an order can be carried out, we guarantee that your personal data will be recorded, saved and treated with utmost care and in compliance with the relevant laws.

When you access our internet pages, we receive user data. We use this data, but in all cases respect the highest standards of security of the teleservice data protection law (TDDSG) and the data protection directive for telecommunication companies (TDSV). This rules out that user data or user profiles can be connected with personal data and thus the creation of a "transparent user".

## Your Consent

By using favicon.cc, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. As Xoron GmbH is constantly enlarging its offering, changes may occur. We recommend therefore that you read this guideline regularly.
